question_data = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "In &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure&quot;, "
                        "Father Enrico Pucchi uses a total of 3 stands in Part 6: Stone Ocean.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "The protagonist in &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; "
                        "has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Deviluke.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "The animated film &quot;Spirited Away&quot; "
                        "won the Academy Award for Best Animated Feature at the 75th Academy Awards in 2003.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
